Guide to the Office of the University Treasurer records, 1893-ongoing UA.10.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Duke Endowment, 1915-1957, Rural Churches, 1927-1969, James B. Duke Superannuate Fund, 1915-1955, Trustees' Records, 1924-1954
  - 1927-1969 (Box 12)
    - Stonewall Church, Pamlico Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Swansboro Church, Swansboro Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 12)
    - The Duke Endowment -- Rural Church (Box 12)
  - 1915-1955 (Box 13)
    - J. B. Duke Superannuate Checks -- Lists (Box 13)
    - R. L. Flowers and Alex H. Sands, Jr., Trustees (Box 13)
    - Columbia College -- R. L. Flowers, Trustee (Box 13)
    - Carr Methodist Church -- R. L. Flowers, Trustee (Box 13)
    - R. L. Flowers, Trustee -- Lincoln Hospital (Box 13)
    - R. L. Flowers -- Oxford Orphanage (Box 13)
    - R. L. Flowers, Alex H. Sands, Jr., and Thomas G. Neal, Trustees (Box 13)
    - G. G. Allen, Alex H. Sands, Jr., R. L. Flowers, Trustees -- Pineland School (Box 13)
    - R. L. Flowers and Alex H. Sands, Jr. -- Laurinburg Normal and Industrial Institute (Box 13)
- Financial Records, 1925-1949
  Boxes 14-19 contain accession A82-132.
  - Budget, 1927-1940 (Box 14)
  - Budget, 1941-1948 (Box 15)
  - School of Medicine, 1933-1947 (Box 15)
  - Salary Budget, 1926-1949 (Box 16)
  - 1925-1948 (Box 17)
    - Report on Audit for the Year Ended 30 June 1925 (Box 17)
    - Duke University Haberdashery (Box 17)
    - Duke University Laundry (Box 17)
    - Duke University Union (Box 17)
    - Duke University Development Fund (Box 17)
    - Duke University Press (Box 17)
    - Alumni Fund (Box 17)
    - Athletic Association -- Trial Balance (Box 17)
    - Physical War Research (Box 17)
    - Chart of Accounts (Box 17)
  - 1923-1948 (Box 18)
    - Income and Expense Statements for 1923-1925 (Box 18)
    - The Archive (Box 18)
    - The Chanticleer (Box 18)
    - The Chronicle (Box 18)
    - Duke 'N' Duchess (Box 18)
    - Cost -- Data (Box 18)
    - Cost Statements -- Hospital (Box 18)
    - Duke University Instrument Shop (Box 18)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems (Box 18)
    - Typing Bureau (Box 18)
    - Special Activities -- Trial Balances (Box 18)
    - Duke University Investments (Box 18)
- G. C. Hendricksen Subject Files, 1944-1970
  Box 19 contains accession A72-22. Box 20 contains accessions A72-22 and A72-42.
  - 1944-1970 (Box 19)
    - Faculty and Staff Benefit Study Ad Hoc Committee (Box 19)
    - Faculty Benefits Committee (Box 19)
    - Faculty Benefits Handbook (Box 19)
    - Ford Profile (Box 19)
    - Ford Foundation Grants (Box 19)
    - Gifts and Grants (Box 19)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (Box 19)
    - Grievances (Box 19)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (Box 19)
    - Hospital Care thru 1968 (Box 19)
    - Hoyler -- Coordinator of Data Processing (Box 19)
    - Hyperbaric (Box 19)
    - Journals, Medical Care Faculty Emeriti (Box 19)
    - NACUBO (Box 19)
    - Personnel Policy Committee (Box 19)
    - Highland Hospital, Inc. -- Medical Director's Report (Box 19)
    - Highland Hospital, Inc. (Box 19)
    - Highland Hospital -- Constitution and By-laws (Box 19)
    - Highland Hospital -- Minutes of the Board of Directors Meeting (Box 19)
    - Highland Hospital -- Minutes of the Board of Directors Meeting (Box 19)
  - 1960-1969 (Box 20)
    - Barton Gillet Company -- Analysis and Appraisal of Communications (Box 20)
    - University Council -- Committee on Communication with the Public (Box 20)
    - Business Division -- Reports (Box 20)
    - Duke University Athletic Council (Box 20)
    - Dining Halls (Box 20)
    - Dining Halls -- Woman's College (Box 20)
    - Employee Performance Report (Box 20)
    - Marine Lab (Box 20)
    - Duke University Press (Box 20)
    - Duke University Stores (Box 20)
    - Durham Investment Corporation (Box 20)
    - Educational Facilities Committee (Box 20)
    - Educational Facilities Laboratory (Box 20)
    - Educational TV (Box 20)
    - EIP (Box 20)
    - Engineering (Box 20)
    - Executive Committee (Box 20)
- A. S. Brower and G. C. Hendricksen Subject Files, 1937-1979
  Boxes 21-30 contain accession A93-102.
  - 1931-1959 (Box 21)
    - Ackland, W. H. -- Art Museum (Box 21)
    - Admissions Statistics (Box 21)
    - Aesthetics, Art and Music, Dept. of (Box 21)
    - Alumni Affairs (Box 21)
    - Alumni Affairs, C. A. Dukes (Box 21)
    - Angier Duke Regional Scholarships (Box 21)
    - Army (Box 21)
    - Barber Collection (Box 21)
    - Barnes, J. Foster [Director of Choral Music] (Box 21)
    - Budget (Box 21)
    - Christian Convocation (Box 21)
    - Class Rings -- Contract (Box 21)
    - Classroom Study (Box 21)
    - Commencement Committee (Box 21)
    - Community Chest -- Budget (Box 21)
    - Community Chest -- Budget Committee (Box 21)
    - Concert Series -- Contracts (Box 21)
    - Degrees Held by Faculty and Librarians (Box 21)
    - Dining Halls -- T. W. Minah (Box 21)
    - Divinity School (Box 21)
    - Divinity School -- James L .Gray Fund (Box 21)
  - 1944-1966 (Box 22)
    - Dozier, John The Relationship of Duke University to Teachers (Box 22)
    - Duke Development Program -- Individual Gift Reports (Box 22)
    - Duke Development Program -- Balance of Pledge of Mr. Edgar S. Bowling (Box 22)
    - Duke Endowment -- R. E. Dumont (Box 22)
    - Duke Family, Donations from (Box 22)
    - Duke Hospital -- Miscellaneous Reports, etc. (Box 22)
    - Duke Hospital -- Patients Discharged, statistics (Box 22)
    - Duke University Hospital (Box 22)
    - Duke Medical Center Fund (Box 22)
    - Duke University Loyalty Fund (Box 22)
    - Duke University Medical Center Collection Agency (Box 22)
    - Duke University National Council -- Constitution and By-laws (Box 22)
    - Duke University National Council -- Correspondence (Box 22)
    - Duke University National Council -- Membership and Committee Appointments (Box 22)
    - Duke University National Council -- Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Duke University Seal, Use of (Box 22)
    - Edens, Arthur Hollis (Box 22)
    - Edens, Arthur Hollis -- Inauguration (Box 22)
    - Edens Reception Mailing List (Box 22)
    - Education, Department of (Box 22)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 22)
    - Elkins, Durham and Kemp (Box 22)
    - Engineering, Science and Management War Training Courses, 1940-1945 (Box 22)
    - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees -- Agendas (Box 22)
  - 1935-1955 (Box 23)
    - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees -- Agendas and other Documents (Box 23)
    - Expendable Special Funds -- Letters (Box 23)
    - Faculty and Administrators (Box 23)
    - Fidelity Bank (Box 23)
    - Financial Reports [includes mailing lists] (Box 23)
    - Financial Reports -- Worksheets (Box 23)
    - Financial Tabulations -- Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - German Indoctrination Program (Box 23)
    - German Law Trainees (Box 23)
    - German Student Scholarships (Box 23)
    - Gottsman Foundation Fund, Walter Kempner (Box 23)
    - Graduate Dormitory (Box 23)
    - Grout, A. J. -- Herbarium (Box 23)
    - Harvard-Duke Cooperative Training Program for Foreign Teachers of American Literature (Box 23)
    - Halsted, Edward Bayard (Box 23)
    - Higher Education -- Publications, Correspondence, etc. (Box 23)
    - Hospital Care Association (Box 23)
    - Hospital Care Administration (Box 23)
  - 1948-1967 (Box 24)
    - Hospital Care Association, 1948-1955 (Box 24)
    - Hospital Care Association -- Material for Chicago (Box 24)
    - Hospital -- Audit and Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Hospital Equipment -- Yearly Budget Lists (Box 24)
    - Hospital Survey (Box 24)
    - Housing (Box 24)
    - Housing -- Faculty and Students (Box 24)
    - Housing -- Edwin L. Jones (Box 24)
    - Housing Proposal, New York Life (Box 24)
    - Inn [housing] Proposal -- A. Paterno (Box 24)
    - Institute of International Education (Box 24)
    - Institutional Studies -- Reports (Box 24)
  - 1940-1969 (Box 25)
    - Institutional Studies -- Reports (Box 25)
    - Law School (Box 25)
    - Library (Box 25)
    - Loyalty Fund -- Charles A. Dukes (Box 25)
    - Marine Biological Laboratories (Box 25)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 25)
    - Medical School (Box 25)
    - Navy -- Sanitary Reports (Box 25)
    - Nearly New Shoppe - Proposed By-law for Medical School Faculty Wives (Box 25)
    - New Buildings, Estimated Expenditures on, SW Myatt (Box 25)
    - North Carolina Medical Care Commission (Box 25)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 25)
    - Page Auditorium (Box 25)
    - Patent Policies (Box 25)
    - Patent Policy Committee (Box 25)
    - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co. (Box 25)
    - Post Office, East Campus (Box 25)
    - Physical War Research, Dept. of (Box 25)
    - Physics Department (Box 25)
    - Press Committee (Box 25)
    - Prisoners of War -- Contracts (Box 25)
    - Research Grant Budgets (Box 25)
    - Research Triangle Park (Box 25)
  - 1940-1968 (Box 26)
    - Research Triangle Park (Box 26)
    - Retirement Plan (Box 26)
    - Retirement, Pensions, Insurance, etc. (Box 26)
    - Rowe, Goodin, Jones, Contract Info., Bureau of (Box 26)
    - Salaries -- Faculty, Comparisons with other institutions (Box 26)
    - Salary Memoranda -- Death and Retirement (Box 26)
    - Sands, Alexander H., Jr. (Box 26)
    - Scholarship Committee (Box 26)
    - Scholarships and Fellowship -- Miscellaneous (Box 26)
    - Scholarships -- Angier Duke Graduate Awards and Fellowships, etc. (Box 26)
    - School of Forestry (Box 26)
    - Selective Science (Box 26)
    - Senior Class, June 1952 Project -- Erection of Stone Bulletin Board (Box 26)
    - Senior Class of 1953 -- Project (Box 26)
    - Shea, Vincent (Box 26)
    - Smith, Willis, Chairman, Board of Trustees (Box 26)
    - Solicitation and Selling on Campus Committee (Box 26)
    - Southern Association of College and University Business Officers Institute (Box 26)
    - Southern Regional Education Board -- Information re: meeting in Atlanta 1952 (Box 26)
    - Sponsors for Hebrew Scrolls (Box 26)
    - Statistics -- Enrollment, War Contributions, etc. (Box 26)
    - Statistics -- General (Box 26)
    - Stores, J. D. Wellons (Box 26)
    - Student Loans at Duke University (Box 26)
    - Summer Session (Box 26)
    - Student Activities Building and Union Building (Box 26)
    - Taxes (Box 26)
  - 1937-1962 (Box 27)
    - Taxes (Box 27)
    - Taxes -- Letters and Other Data Concerning Tax Exemption for Foreign Students (Box 27)
    - Taxes -- Mills Bill (Box 27)
    - Telephone System (Box 27)
    - Torch Club (Box 27)
    - Trustee Reports (Box 27)
    - Tuition and Fees -- Changes, etc. (Box 27)
    - University Research Council (Box 27)
    - Union Manager -- Correspondence (Box 27)
    - V-12, Union -- Correspondence (Box 27)
    - V-12, Union -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
    - Woman's College (Box 27)
    - General Correspondence (Box 27)
  - 1942-1971 (Box 28)
    - General Correspondence (Box 28)
    - Administrative Council -- Correspondence, etc. (Box 28)
    - Admissions Statistics and Applications Analysis (Box 28)
    - American Association of University Professors -- Duke University Chapter (Box 28)
    - Banking Facility Committee (Box 28)
    - Bowers, H. Frank (Box 28)
    - Bryson, E. C., University Counsel (Box 28)
    - Chanticleer (Box 28)
    - The Common Fund (Box 28)
    - Duke Hospital -- Louis Swanson (Box 28)
    - Duke Hospital -- General Correspondence and Newsletter (Box 28)
    - Ford Foundation Grant (Box 28)
    - Fringe Benefit -- Medical Examinations for Staff (Box 28)
    - Graduate and Post-graduate Fellowships and Assistantships -- Tax Ruling (Box 28)
    - Duke, James B. Fellowships (Box 28)
    - Hospital Statements (Box 28)
    - Intercom [Medical Center Newsletter] (Box 28)
    - Married Student Housing (Box 28)
    - NCNB -- Undergraduate Dorms [Edens] (Box 28)
  - 1960-1975 (Box 29)
    - Medical Center Administration (Box 29)
    - Patents (Box 29)
    - Rauch, Henry E. (Box 29)
    - Steinert, Jeff (Box 29)
    - Tuition Plan (Box 29)
    - Student Loans at Duke University (Box 29)
    - Scholarships -- Angier Duke Graduate Awards and Fellowships, etc. (Box 29)
    - Taxes (Box 29)
    - Tuition Plan (Box 29)
    - University Planning Committee (Box 29)
    - University Policy Planning and Advisory Committee (Box 29)
    - University Planning Committee and Graduate Affairs Committee, Report -- The Graduate School (Box 29)
    - Adelia S. Parks -- Loan (Box 29)
    - Bindewald, Richard A. (Box 29)
    - Commencement (Box 29)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Housing (Box 29)
    - Divinity School (Box 29)
    - Divinity School -- Tuition Plan (Box 29)
    - Duke Hospital -- General Correspondence (Box 29)
    - Duke Hospital -- General Correspondence and Newsletters (Box 29)
    - Duke Hospital -- General Correspondence and Reports (Box 29)
    - Duke Hospital -- General (Box 29)
    - Harward, S.C., Misc. Workpapers [Henry E. Rauch] (Box 29)
    - Main LaFrentz and Co. -- Duke Endowment (Box 29)
    - Montreal, Inc. (Box 29)
    - OSHA (Box 29)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 30)
    - OTS [Organization for Tropical Studies] (Box 30)
    - Options -- Irving Trust (Box 30)
    - Option -- Writing (Box 30)
- Gift Records, 1908-1970
  Box 31 contains accession A93-113.
  - William Hayes Ackland -- Last Will and Testament and Statement of Account of the American Security and Trust Company and Edson B. Olds, Jr., Executors of the Estate of William Hayes Ackland, 1938-1941 (Box 31)
  - G. G. Allen Portrait, 1955 (Box 31)
  - Thomas H. Anderson, Will of, 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - John Spencer Bassett Memorial, 1964 (Box 31)
  - William Perry Bentley and Wife Trust for Parapsychology, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Blue Bird Taxi Agreement, 1939-1940 (Box 31)
  - Celeste W. and Kenneth M. Blake, 1962 (Box 31)
  - John Alonzo Bolich, Jr. Codicil and Will, 1961 (Box 31)
  - Brewer-Burch Matter re: Gifts for Scholarship, 1961-1966 (Box 31)
  - Edgar S. Bowling, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Elizabeth M. Brigham Estate, 1954-1958 (Box 31)
  - Portrait -- E.C. Brooks [Class of 1916], 1937 (Box 31)
  - College Life Insurance Company of America, 1952 (Box 31)
  - Duke Homestead, 1939 (Box 31)
  - Elizabeth M. Dickerman, Estate, 1962 (Box 31)
  - J.B. Duke Building Fund, 1924-1931 (Box 31)
  - James B. Duke Desk, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Estate [incl. official appraisals of items donated to Duke], 1942-1961 (Box 31)
  - Mrs. Nanaline H. Duke and Miss Doris Duke Gothic Tapestry Panels, 1953-1956 (Box 31)
  - Washington Duke Chair, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Nanaline H. Duke Trust Indenture, 1934-1970 (Box 31)
  - Washington Duke Memorial Statue, 1937 (Box 31)
  - Durham Coca-Cola Bottling Company, 1930 (Box 31)
  - Dwire, Henry R. Last Will and Testament, 1944 (Box 31)
  - Farmers Mutual Exchange, 1940-1945 (Box 31)
  - William C. Ferguson, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Mrs. Alexander J. Felig, Parapsychology Laboratory, 1960 (Box 31)
  - Claude M. Flowers Will, 1953-1956 (Box 31)
  - Edwin D. Fowler, 1958-1960 (Box 31)
  - General Education Board -- Proposition, 1908-1915 (Box 31)
  - C. Leon Gibbs Trust, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Gift for Purchase of Radio Telephone Transmitter, 1936 (Box 31)
  - Gifts -- Unfinished Business, 1941-1947 (Box 31)
  - Hamlin and Abernathy Property near Beaufort, NC, 1935-1941 (Box 31)
  - P. Haber Hanes Will, 1967 (Box 31)
  - Hart, Daryl, Gift, 1964 (Box 31)
  - Hart, Dr. Deryl, Patent [Sterilamp], 1936-1950 (Box 31)
  - John M. W. Hicks Last Will and Testament, 1945 (Box 31)
  - Highland Hospital [Asheville, NC -- includes photographs], 1938-1949 (Box 31)
  - Thomas H. Hockstader Will, 1967 (Box 31)
  - Willard T. Kniffin, 1963-1965 (Box 31)
  - Estate of Robert F. Kneipp, 1973-1974 (Box 31)
  - Dr. Hedwig Kohn, Bequest, 1964 (Box 31)
  - William T. Laprade Will, 1974 (Box 31)
  - William Reynolds Lybrook, 1964 (Box 31)
  - Marion S. Lewis, 1964 (Box 31)
  - E. Buchanan Lyon, 1949 (Box 31)
  - Helen Maher Trust, 1946-1973 (Box 31)
  - C.R. Matheson, 1964 (Box 31)
  - Frank H. Menaker Bequest, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
  - David D. Milne Codicil to Will, 1961 (Box 31)
  - Donald Walcutt Mitchell, 1964 (Box 31)
  - R.J. Morris, 1964 (Box 31)
  - New Endowment Fund, 1923-1945 (Box 31)
  - Dr. H.M. North Gift of Books, 1932-1937 (Box 31)
  - Will of Charles E. Ozanne, 1948 (Box 31)
  - Wilhelmina H. Pearson Will, 1962 (Box 31)
  - Fidelity Bank Statements, 1940-1941 (Box 31)
  - E.C. Register Estate, 1928-1931 (Box 31)
  - Radium Loan -- USPHS Duke Hospital, 1949-1964 (Box 31)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Trent Gifts [including Walt Whitman collection], 1942-1965 (Box 31)
  - Hiram N. Slemaker -- Will, 1959 (Box 31)
  - Wills of Herman and Tommie Lou Smith, 1962 (Box 31)
  - Trent Collection of Medical Books and Manuscripts, 1955-1970 (Box 31)
  - Norman Van Nostrand, 1952-1956 (Box 31)
  - Will of Frank Wall, 1946 (Box 31)
  - Washington, DC Bicentennial Award, 1932 (Box 31)
  - Leon F. Williams, 1962 (Box 31)
- Oversize - Boxed Ledgers and Account Books 1911-1982
  This series includes accession A70-79, A91-125, UA2006-29, UA2009-0005, and UA2014.0084.
  - Payroll Ledger, 1927-1928 (Box 32)
  - Payroll Ledger, 1930 (Box 33)
  - Payroll Ledger (Box 34)
  - Schedule of Salary Increments, 1961-1963 (Box 34)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Personnel records restricted until 2033.
  - Ledgers, 1911-1956 (Box 35)
    - Shipping Book and Receipt Book (Box 35)
    - Library Accounts Ledger (Box 35)
    - Renters and Employees (Box 35)
    - Insurance Records (Box 35)
    - Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship Fund Ledger (Box 35)
    - Development Fund Subscriptions (Box 35)
    - Renovation and Construction Ledger (Box 35)
  - Ledgers, 1926-1946 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous Expenditures (Box 36)
    - Sales and Purchases Journal (Box 36)
  - Ledgers, 1930-1937 (Box 37)
    - Student Athletic and Delinquent Book, vol. 1 and 2 (Box 37)
  - Account Books, 1937-1943 (Box 38)
    - Student Athletic and Delinquent Book, vol. 3 and 4 (Box 38)
  - Ledgers, 1940-1947 (Box 39)
    - Student Accounts (Box 39)
    - Student Course Loads (Box 39)
    - Index (Box 39)
    - Student Accounts (Box 39)
    - Navy Program Cadet Corps (Box 39)
  - Account Books, 1927-1949 (Box 40)
    - Payroll Account (Box 40)
    - Alumni Fund (Box 40)
    - Expenditures (Box 40)
  - Student Account Books, 1925-1926 (Box 42)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1949-1952 (Box 43)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1953-1956 (Box 44)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1957-1959 (Box 45)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1960-1961 (Box 46)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1962 (Box 47)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1963 (Box 48)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1964 (Box 49)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1965 (Box 50)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1966 (Box 51)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1966-1967 (Box 52)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1967 (Box 53)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1968 (Box 54)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1969 (Box 55)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1970 (Box 56)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1971 (Box 57)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1972 (Box 58)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1973 (Box 59)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1974 (Box 60)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1974 (Box 61)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1975-1976 (Box 62)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1977-1978 (Box 63)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1979 (Box 64)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1981 (Box 66)
  - Individual Fund Statement, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Summary and Trial Balance, 1960, 1961, 1963 (Box 68)
  - Summary Financial Statements, 1958-1960 (Box 69)
  - Summary Financial Statements, 1961-1964 (Box 70)
  - Summary Financial Statements, 1965 (Box 71)
  - Summary Financial Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 72)
  - Endowed Funds, 1958, 1960 (Box 73)
  - Endowed Funds, 1961-1962 (Box 74)
  - Endowed Funds, 1963-1964 (Box 75)
  - Endowed Funds, 1965; Detailed Revenue, 1930-1932 (Box 76)
  - Detailed Revenue, 1932-1935 (Box 77)
  - Detailed Revenue, 1935-1938 (Box 78)
  - Detailed Revenue, 1938-1941 (Box 79)
  - Detailed Revenue, 1942-1945 (Box 80)
  - Detailed Revenue, 1945-1946; Report on Examination of Accounts, 1950-1957 (Box 81)
  - Report on Examination of Accounts, 1958-1960, 1971-1974 (Box 82)
  - Report on Audit, 1932-1941 (Box 83)
  - Report on Audit, 1942-1949 (Box 84)
  - Duke University Financial Report (alternate title of Annual Report, 1948-2001 [publicly distributed and therefore not restricted]; Independent Auditor's Report, 1995, 1996; Payroll Procedures, circa 1970s (Box 85)
  - Voucher register 2, July 1, 1930 - May 4, 1932 (Box 86)
  - Voucher register 3, May 4, 1932 - April 9, 1934 (Box 87)
  - Voucher register 4, April 9, 1934 - November 20, 1935 (Box 88)
  - Voucher register 5, November 30, 1935 - July 21, 1937 (Box 89)
  - Voucher register 6, July 22, 1937 - May 23, 1939 (Box 90)
  - Voucher register 7, May 24, 1939 - June 30, 1940 (Box 91)
  - Voucher register 8, July 1, 1940 - June 30, 1941 (Box 92)
  - Voucher register 9, July 1, 1941 - June 30, 1942 (Box 93)
  - Voucher register 10, July 1, 1942 - June 30, 1943 (Box 94)
  - Voucher register 11, July 1, 1943 - June 30, 1944 (Box 95)
  - Voucher register 12, July 1, 1944 - June 30, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Voucher register 13, July 1, 1945 - June 30, 1946 (Box 97)
  - Voucher register 14, July 1, 1946 - June 30, 1947 (Box 98)
  - Voucher register 15, July 1, 1947 - June 30, 1948 (Box 99)
  - Voucher register 16, July 1, 1948 - June 30, 1949 (Box 100)
  - Voucher register 17, July 1, 1949 - December 31, 1949 (Box 101)
  - Voucher register 18, January 1, 1950 - June 30, 1950 (Box 102)
  - Voucher register 19, 1950 July 1 - 1951 June 30 (Box 103)
  - Voucher register 20, 1951 July 31 - 1952 June 30 (Box 104)
  - Voucher register 21, July 1, 1952 - December 31, 1952 (Box 105)
  - Voucher register, January 1, 1953 - June 30, 1953 (Box 106)
  - Voucher register, November 1953 - February 1954 (Box 108)
  - Voucher register, March 1954 - June 1954 (Box 109)
  - Voucher register, July 1954 - December 1954 (Box 110)
  - Voucher register, January 1955 - May 1955 (Box 111)
  - Voucher register, June 1955 - October 1955 (Box 112)
  - Voucher register, November 1955 - February 1956 (Box 113)
  - Voucher register, March 1956 - June 1956 (Box 114)
  - Voucher register, July 1956 - October 1956 (Box 115)
  - Voucher register, November 1956 - February 1957 (Box 116)
  - Voucher register, March 1957 - June 1957 (Box 117)
  - Voucher register, July 1957 - November 1957 (Box 118)
  - Voucher register, December 1957 - February 1958 (Box 119)
  - Voucher register, March 1958 - June 1958 (Box 120)
  - Voucher register, July 1958 - October 1958 (Box 121)
  - Voucher register, May 1959 - June 1959 (Box 123)
  - Voucher register, July 1960 - October 1960 (Box 124)
  - Voucher register, October 1960 - February 1961 (Box 125)
  - Voucher register, March 1961 - June 1961 (Box 126)
  - Budget statements, 1950-1954 (Box 107)
  - Funds disbursements, July 1956 - June 1960 (Box 123)
  - Receipts and disbursements, July 1, 1946 - June 30, 1948 (Box 122)
  - Cash receipts, July 1948 - February 1957 (Box 127)
  - Transfer Journal, 1950 July 1 - 1953 August 30 (Box 128)
  - Transfer Journal, 1953 July - 1955 June (Box 129)
  - Transfer Journal, 1955 July - 1957 June (Box 130)
  - Expenditures Trial Balances, 1953-1954 (Box 131)
- Oversize - Unboxed Materials (housed on-site, see catalog for location), 1893-1956
  - Expendable Funds F-M, 1924-1949 (Volume 1)
  - Scholarship Funds, 1928-1954 (Volume 2)
  - Expendable and Endowment Funds, 1927-1956 (Volume 3)
  - Cash Book, 1907 (Volume 4)
  - Miscellaneous Funds, 1920-1924 (Volume 4)
  - Stock Investment Records, 1902-1913 (Volume 4)
  - Financial Records, 1916-1920 (Volume 5)
  - Scholarship Funds and Real Estate Transactions, 1893-1956 (Volume 6)